wmhaven.com 2011-05-15

# 

Wmhaven.com is committed to user privacy in its products and services. This policy outlines our personal information handling practices. If you give us personal information, we will treat it according to this policy. 

This policy covers Wmhaven.com's web site. Wmhaven.com encourages you to read this privacy policy and those of all web sites you visit. Below is a summary of Wmhaven.com's online privacy policy. 

_

## Types and uses of personal information

_

  * Customer Feedback and Support. 
    * Provides a mechanism for requesting information from Wmhaven.com Also used to tell us how we can improve our products, services and site designs. 
  * Email Correspondence. 
    * Used to raise and respond to issues and inquiries of all types. Also used to distribute information about Wmhaven.com, our products, and services. 
  * Services Purchase 
    * Payment transactions for directory submissions are handled by 2Checkout. Information collected by this payment method are stored **by this exclusive authorized retailer of our services** , providing the transaction services and Wmhaven.com has no access to your credit card details other than your name, phone number and mailing address which is necessary to complete the Services. 
    * Refunds:
             You have only 24H to cancel or change your order and ask for refund.  

_

## Security Measures

_   
We protect the personal information you share with us. Access to your personal information is limited to people who need it to do their job. 

_

## Linked Web Sites

_   
We provide links to third party sites. Since we do not control these Web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third party sites.
